<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"><url><loc>/posts/it-stem-summer-camp-9th-grade-students-june-2025/</loc><lastmod>2025-05-06T18:18:52-06:00</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Calling all incoming 9th grade students interested in information technology! The IT STEM summer camp will be June 10th - June 20th, 2025 (Tuesday - Friday), 8:00 AM – 12:00 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College Build, code, and explore with hands-on Raspberry Pi projects, computer teardown, cyber security, and programming. Get ready to jumpstart your future in tech!</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/cache-tech-community-meetup-feburuary-2025/</loc><lastmod>2025-01-18T00:16:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Join us on Feb 22, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College for a tech meetup focused on programming and networking. The event features an open discussion on tech careers and a hands-on session where attendees will build a chat application in Go. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop and curiosity!</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/</loc><lastmod>2025-01-18T00:16:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Join us on Jan 25, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Logan Library for a tech meetup! The event features an open discussion on tech careers and a deep dive into mobile forensics, including an iPhone forensic demo. Open to all skill levels—come learn and connect!</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/why-you-should-join-our-discord/</loc><lastmod>2025-01-18T00:15:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Join our official Discord server to stay updated, connect with like-minded individuals, ask questions, showcase your projects, and collaborate with the community. Gain access to exclusive events, discussions, and networking opportunities. Be part of a dynamic and supportive space—join today!</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/how-to-spot-and-avoid-scams/</loc><lastmod>2025-01-18T00:00:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Scams use urgency, emotional manipulation, and too-good-to-be-true offers to deceive victims. Avoid falling for them by verifying sources, being cautious with unsolicited messages, and protecting personal information. Watch for red flags like suspicious payment methods and unprofessional communication. Stay vigilant, trust your instincts, and report any suspicious activity.</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/cache-tech-community-meetup-june-2025/</loc><lastmod>2025-06-27T00:16:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Join us on June 28th, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College for a tech meetup focused on Raspberry Pi. The event features an open discussion on tech careers and a presentation on Raspberry Pi. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop, Raspberry Pi if you have one, and curiosity!</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/cache-tech-community-meetup-may-2025/</loc><lastmod>2025-05-19T00:16:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Join us on May 24th, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College for a tech meetup focused on DNS. The event features an open discussion on tech careers and a deep dive into DNS security vulnerabilities. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop and curiosity!</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/cache-tech-community-meetup-april-2025/</loc><lastmod>2025-04-14T00:16:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Join us on April 26, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College for a tech meetup focused on self-hosting and privacy. The event features an open discussion on tech careers and a hands-on demo where attendees will learn to self-host applications using Coolify. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop and curiosity!</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/cache-tech-community-meetup-march-2025/</loc><lastmod>2025-03-13T00:16:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority><xhtml:summary>Join us on March 22, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College for a tech meetup focused on programming and networking. The event features an open discussion on tech careers and a hands-on session where attendees will secure an application in Go*. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop and curiosity!</xhtml:summary></url><url><loc>/posts/</loc><lastmod>2025-08-15T00:16:00Z</lastmod><changefreq>weekly</changefreq><priority>0.5</priority></url></urlset>