<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Cache Valley Communities</title><link>/p/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Cache Valley Communities</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/p/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tree Planting Volunteer Opportunity with Northwestern Band of the Shoshone Nation</title><link>/p/nwbshoshone-tree-planting-2025/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/nwbshoshone-tree-planting-2025/</guid><description>Join the Northwestern Band of the Shoshone Nation on November 7th and 8th for a tree-planting weekend at the Bear River Massacre site in Idaho. Help restore the land with native plants and support long-term ecological recovery.</description></item><item><title>IT STEM Summer Camp (9th Grade Students) - June 2025</title><link>/p/it-stem-summer-camp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:18:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>/p/it-stem-summer-camp/</guid><description>Calling all incoming 9th grade students interested in &lt;strong&gt;information technology!&lt;/strong&gt; The &lt;strong&gt;IT STEM summer camp&lt;/strong&gt; will be &lt;strong&gt;June 10th - June 20th, 2025 (Tuesday - Friday)&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;8:00 AM – 12:00 PM (MST)&lt;/strong&gt; at &lt;strong&gt;Bridgerland Technical College&lt;/strong&gt; Build, code, and explore with hands-on &lt;strong&gt;Raspberry Pi projects, computer teardown, cyber security, and programming&lt;/strong&gt;. Get ready to jumpstart your future in tech!</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - Feburuary 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-february-2025/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-february-2025/</guid><description>Join us on &lt;strong&gt;Feb 22, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College&lt;/strong&gt; for a tech meetup focused on &lt;strong&gt;programming and networking&lt;/strong&gt;. The event features an &lt;strong&gt;open discussion on tech careers&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;hands-on session&lt;/strong&gt; where attendees will &lt;strong&gt;build a chat application in Go&lt;/strong&gt;. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop and curiosity!</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - January 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2025/</guid><description>Join us on Jan 25, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Logan Library for a tech meetup! The event features an open discussion on tech careers and a deep dive into mobile forensics, including an iPhone forensic demo. Open to all skill levels—come learn and connect!</description></item><item><title>Why You Should Join Our Official Discord Server</title><link>/p/why-you-should-join-our-discord/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/why-you-should-join-our-discord/</guid><description>Join our official Discord server to stay updated, connect with like-minded individuals, ask questions, showcase your projects, and collaborate with the community. Gain access to exclusive events, discussions, and networking opportunities. Be part of a dynamic and supportive space—join today!</description></item><item><title>How to Spot and Avoid Scams</title><link>/p/how-to-spot-and-avoid-scams/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/how-to-spot-and-avoid-scams/</guid><description>Scams use urgency, emotional manipulation, and too-good-to-be-true offers to deceive victims. Avoid falling for them by verifying sources, being cautious with unsolicited messages, and protecting personal information. Watch for red flags like suspicious payment methods and unprofessional communication. Stay vigilant, trust your instincts, and report any suspicious activity.</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community - RAM Fundementals &amp; Community Projects Showcase - January 2026</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2026/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-january-2026/</guid><description>Join us on Saturday, January 24th, 2026, from 1:30 PM to 3:30 PM at Bridgerland Technical College for our Cache Tech Community RAM Fundementals &amp;amp; Community Projects Showcase! This event will feature a presentation on the fundamentals of RAM and a showcase of projects from our community!</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community OSINT Workshop - October 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-community-meetup-october-2025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-community-meetup-october-2025/</guid><description>Join us on Friday, October 25th, 2025, from 1:30 PM to 3:30 PM at Bridgerland Technical College for our Cache Tech Community OSINT workshop! This follow-up presentation focuses on protecting yourself from OSINT techniques and minimizing your digital footprint. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re concerned about privacy, security, or just want to understand how to control your digital presence, this presentation will provide practical, actionable steps to enhance your digital privacy.</description></item><item><title>DIY Mobile Verification Toolkit (MVT) Workshop</title><link>/p/intro-to-mobile-forensics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/intro-to-mobile-forensics/</guid><description>A self-paced, hands-on workshop on using the Mobile Verification Toolkit (MVT) for ethical mobile forensics. Complete it anytime. Occasional in-person sessions may be offered separately.</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community OSINT Workshop - September 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-september-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-september-2025/</guid><description>Join us on Saturday, September 27th, 2025, from 1:30 PM to 3:30 PM at Bridgerland Technical College for our Cache Tech Community OSINT workshop! This hands-on workshop will teach you OSINT (Open Source Intelligence) techniques that you can use in investigations, journalism, and cybersecurity. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer, student, or tech enthusiast, this event is perfect for anyone interested in learning information gathering skills and networking within Cache Valley&amp;rsquo;s tech scene.</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - August 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-august-2025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-august-2025/</guid><description>Join us on &lt;strong&gt;August 23rd, 2025&lt;/strong&gt; for a special Cache Tech Community meetup featuring &lt;strong&gt;CodeCamp: Bridgerland winners presenting their incredible projects&lt;/strong&gt;! Come celebrate their achievements and connect with Cache Valley&amp;rsquo;s amazing tech community. Open to everyone—whether you participated in CodeCamp or just want to see some awesome projects!</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - June 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-june-2025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-june-2025/</guid><description>Join us on &lt;strong&gt;June 28th, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College&lt;/strong&gt; for a tech meetup focused on &lt;strong&gt;Raspberry Pi&lt;/strong&gt;. The event features an &lt;strong&gt;open discussion on tech careers&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;presentation on Raspberry Pi&lt;/strong&gt;. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop, Raspberry Pi if you have one, and curiosity!</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - May 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-may-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-may-2025/</guid><description>Join us on &lt;strong&gt;May 24th, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College&lt;/strong&gt; for a tech meetup focused on &lt;strong&gt;DNS&lt;/strong&gt;. The event features an &lt;strong&gt;open discussion on tech careers&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;deep dive into DNS security vulnerabilities&lt;/strong&gt;. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop and curiosity!</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - April 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-april-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-april-2025/</guid><description>Join us on &lt;strong&gt;April 26, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College&lt;/strong&gt; for a tech meetup focused on &lt;strong&gt;self-hosting and privacy&lt;/strong&gt;. The event features an &lt;strong&gt;open discussion on tech careers&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;hands-on demo&lt;/strong&gt; where attendees will learn to &lt;strong&gt;self-host applications using Coolify&lt;/strong&gt;. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop and curiosity!</description></item><item><title>Cache Tech Community Meetup - March 2025</title><link>/p/cache-tech-meetup-march-2025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/cache-tech-meetup-march-2025/</guid><description>Join us on &lt;strong&gt;March 22, 2025, at 1:30 PM (MST) at Bridgerland Technical College&lt;/strong&gt; for a tech meetup focused on &lt;strong&gt;programming and networking&lt;/strong&gt;. The event features an &lt;strong&gt;open discussion on tech careers&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;hands-on session&lt;/strong&gt; where attendees will &lt;em&gt;secure an application in Go&lt;/em&gt;*. Open to all skill levels—bring your laptop and curiosity!</description></item></channel></rss>