<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Organizations on Cache Valley Communities</title><link>/organizations/</link><description>Recent content in Organizations on Cache Valley Communities</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/organizations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cache Valley Communities</title><link>/organizations/cachevalleycommunities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/organizations/cachevalleycommunities/</guid><description>Cache Valley Communities is a volunteer-led organization dedicated to bringing people together through &lt;strong>events, meetups, and workshops&lt;/strong>. Our goal is to &lt;strong>foster connection, learning, and collaboration&lt;/strong> while supporting and uniting existing local groups. By creating an &lt;strong>inclusive and supportive space&lt;/strong>, we aim to strengthen the Cache Valley community for everyone.</description></item><item><title>DC435 - Cyber Security</title><link>/organizations/dc435/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/organizations/dc435/</guid><description>DC435 is a free, community-driven DEFCON group in Cache Valley, UT, focused on InfoSec. Meetings are first Thursdays at 7 PM at Bridgerland Technical College, Logan, UT. Open to all, DC435 fosters learning, collaboration, and respect, with a strict no-harassment policy. Just show up to join!</description></item><item><title>W.A.B. Warming Center</title><link>/organizations/wab-warming-center/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/organizations/wab-warming-center/</guid><description>The W.A.B. Warming Center provides a safe, warm space for unhoused individuals and families in Cache Valley, Utah, during the coldest months. It offers resources, supervision, and support to ensure no one is left unsheltered and alone in winter. Families with children are welcome, with safety agreements in place. Visit their official website to learn more.</description></item></channel></rss>